It seems that you
看来你真的
really want to remarry her.
很想跟她复婚
Then later
那以后
I won't help you
我就不会像上次
like last time.
那样帮你了
I will persuade Wanzhen
我还会劝婉真
to not remarry you.
不要跟你复婚
Why?
为什么
Simple.
很简单啊
Because that
因为
it prevents her from working for me.
耽误她为我工作啊
I don't care about your marriage.
我不管你们的婚姻
I only consider the problem
我只从投资的角度
from the perspective of investment
考虑问题
Look,
你看
over the past eight years
过去八年
in your marriage
你们两个的婚姻生活
Wanzhen was
婉真作为
a full-time housewife.
全职太太在打理
So that you can
所以你才能
started a business without hitch.
心无旁骛地创业成功
You want to make your business big.
你现在事业想要做大
You need financing.
要融资
It'll inevitably add more pressure.
那势必会 更大的压力
You will be busier.
会更忙
If you reunite
你如果重新
with your family and children,
拥有了家庭和孩子
or have more children,
或者更多的孩子
you will need someone
你更得需要有个人
to take care of the family for you.
来帮你照顾家庭
Isn't it?
对不对
But please rest assured,
但是您放心啊
even if we get remarried,
即使是复婚了
I will
我也会
fully support her work all the same.
全力支持她工作的
Can you
你能做到
support Wanzhen be like this
让婉真像现在这样
so that she can work at full stretch?
全力以赴地工作吗
Or you are ready
或者你已经做好准备
prepared to sacrifice
为了家庭
your own work for your family?
牺牲自己的工作时间
As an investor,
那我作为投资人
I have to
我可得
re-evaluate your company.
重新评估下你们蓝海
Mr. Yu,
于总
are you willing to give up
你自己的企业
your own career,
你自己的事业
and your own business?
你舍得放弃吗
Don't worry. I will never do that.
我绝对不会 您放心啊
Then why do you
那你有什么理由
ask Wanzhen to return to the marriage?
让婉真重新走回婚姻
Do you think that remarriage is as simple
你以为复婚只是
as applying for another certificate?
重新领个证那么简单吗
If I were Wanzhen,
如果我是婉真
I won't agree with
这么不划算的事
such a bad deal.
我不会做的
Mr. Yu contributed a lot.
于总真不容易
Just look at him in recent years.
就凭他这几年
He spared no efforts
拼尽全力
to raise finance for Blue Ocean,
为蓝海融资的劲头
I knew
我就知道
what kind of person he is.
他是个什么样的人
Wanzhen,
婉真
aren't you even a little bit touched
这段时间
by what he did for you
他为你做的这些事情
during this period?
你就没有一点点感动吗
Now the tables are turning.
风水轮流转
In the past, I lived in a villa.
以前呢 我在别墅里啊
I cooked every day.
烧饭做菜
He is like a guest.
他就像客人一样
Taking our home a hotel, an inn.
把这家当成了酒店 旅馆
Today, I have become the guest.
那今天我成了客人
I eat and drink, and then go away.
吃完喝完就走了
Then you
那你就
just enjoy this moment.
好好享受这一刻嘛
Why did you call me here to cover for you?
你干吗叫我来救场
And asked me to make up so many lies?
还让我编了一堆瞎话
A meeting with investment banker.
什么见投行的
A friend, or things like that.
朋友之类的
Then, what about you?
你还说我
If it weren't for that "surprise"
要不是上次我们出差
during our last business trip.
你叫他过来搞什么惊喜
which inspired him,
给了他勇气
could this happen?
能有今天这一出吗
You should be responsible.
你得负责任
I knew it would go like this.
我猜到就这样
So, I helped you with it.
所以我帮你搞定了
With what?
搞定什么
I helped you extinguish
我帮你浇灭了于海内心
the small tongue of
那股小小的
flame of remarrying you
正在燃烧的
burning in Yu Hai's heart.
想要跟你复婚的小火苗
What did you tell him?
你怎么跟他说的
I told him, if he wanted to remarry you,
我说如果你想跟她复婚
I wouldn't invest in Blue Ocean.
我就不投蓝海了
He chose Blue Ocean.
他选择了蓝海
For sure?
真的
Generally, it's like this.
大概意思是这样啊
But we didn't talk
但是我们话
that straightforward.
没有说那么直白
I'm not a tyrant.
我又不是霸道总裁
I think Yu Hai didn't think it through.
我觉得于海没有想清楚
Like why you divorced him.
你为什么跟他离婚
He didn't figure it out yet.
他也没有想清楚
In his marriage,
在他婚姻里面
as a father,
他作为一个父亲
and a husband,
和一个丈夫
what he should contribute,
他应该付出什么
what he should be responsible.
他必须承担什么
If these are not considered thoroughly.
你连这些都没有想清楚
how could he get remarried?
你怎么复婚
What, are you hungry?
怎么饿了呀
Are you hungry?
你饿不饿
It smells so good.
太香了
Much better than that steak.
比那个牛排好吃多了
If it was not for Yu Hai's feelings,
我真是顾及于海的面子
I would not say it was delicious.
我才夸那个牛排好吃
Tasty.
好吃
You know why
你知道为什么
I came as soon as
今天你一打电话
you called me today?
我就来了吗
Why?
为什么啊
I worried that
我特别担心啊
you agreed to remarry him
你脑子一热
driven by a momentary impulse.
答应跟他复婚
That's overthinking.
想多了吧
Totally unnecessary.
想多了
Eight years ago,
八年前
you quit for your family.
你就为了家庭离职吧
You are used to sacrifice for love.
你有恋爱脑的倾向
Moreover,
再说了
women of your age
像你这个年纪的女性啊
are not easy to find a partner
从大数据来分析
in terms of the big data.
是不太好找对象的
If you choose someone
你说你找个
younger than you,
比你小的鲜肉
a few years later,
再过几年
he will still be young when you are aged.
你老了他还年轻
If you choose someone older than you,
你找个比你老的
a few years later,
过几年
you have to be his baby-sitter.
他老了你还得照顾他
So, getting back with
所以和自己
with your elite ex-husband
成功的前夫复婚
is a good choice
是个不错的选择
What's wrong with my age?
我这个年纪怎么了
I am at a golden age.
我花一样的年龄
How do you know no good partner for me?
谁说我不好找对象了
I don't bother to find one.
那是我不想找
I don't want to remarry either.
我也不想复婚
Me neither.
我也不想你复婚
I still count on you to make money for me.
你还得给我赚钱呢
I won't let you go so easily.
我可不会轻易地放你走
I knew it!
我就知道
You never thought for me for real.
你不是真心为我着想
It's all for yourself.
就是为你自己
Such a miser!
周扒皮
Whatever you say.
行行行
I am a miser.
周扒皮就周扒皮
Single life is enviable.
单身多好啊
Free, and at ease.
自由自在
Come on.
来
To single life!
为单身干杯
Are you single?
你是单身吗
You have so many suitors.
那么多追求者
I am enjoying their wooing.
我是万花丛中走
But I will stop for no one.
片叶不沾身
All right, all right.
行了 行了啊
Eat your wonton.
你吃你的馄饨吧
Here we go.
来了 来了
Look, look, look.
你看 你看 你看
Fresh cherries, big and sweet cherries.
车厘子新鲜 又大又甜
Level 5.
5个级别的
As big as a pigeon egg!
像鸽子蛋一样
Delicious.
好吃极了
Use this in the morning,
早上用这个
and use this at night.
晚上用这个
Let's stroll down the street.
咱从街头逛到街尾
Shopping from the first store,
从第一家店
to the last store.
买到最后一家店
As long as you like.
只要你喜欢
I used to treat you like a princess.
我之前把你当公主
From now on, I'll take you as a queen.
以后我把你当皇后
As my majesty!
我要把你当女王
You are the most important in my heart.
我心里头你最重要
You are the only woman in my heart.
我的心里只有你
Absolutely no another girl here.
绝对没有她
You shall believe
你要相信
in my words and my heart.
我的心意并不假
Darling.
老婆
I'm so lonely
没你的日子
when you left me.
我真的好孤单
I was all the time,
我无时无刻
I was all the time, thinking about you.
心里时时刻刻都想着你
I was thinking about you when driving.
我开车想着你
I was thinking about you when working.
工作想着你
I was thinking about you even when eating.
吃饭的时候都我想着你
Xin, try some rice cake.
心 米粿买回来啦
Eating sweet will bring you good mood.
吃甜的 心情好
Come on, try some.
来一口 张嘴
No, I am full.
吃不下 吃不下
My darling wants some water.
我的媳妇要喝水
Take a sip, just take a sip.
喝一口 喝一口
It helps you calm down and sleep well.
安神 能睡好觉
Drink it all.
喝完
We haven't dated for a long time.
好久没约会了
I've made a reservation.
我订好地儿了
Candlelight dinner.
烛光晚餐
Well, not bad for that.
这还差不多
My life dream is
我的人生梦想就是
to grow old
跟我心爱的女人
with my beloved.
白头到老
My life dream is to
我的人生梦想
have babies
就是跟我最爱的
with my beloved wife.
女人生宝宝
Stop teasing me! Hit you!
我打你 我打你 我打
Dear,
老婆
I love you.
我爱你呦
Isn't it beautiful?
漂亮吧
I don't want Mom and Dad to divorce.
我不要爸爸妈妈离婚
If that day really comes,
真有那一天的话
I'm telling you, you will
我告诉你
get the house, the car and the deposit.
房子车子存款
They are all yours.
全是你的
I will leave, giving up on everything.
我净身出户
Don't full me.
别给我画饼
Everything here will be split in half.
家里东西都劈两半
We live our own life.
各过各的
After the birth of this baby,
等孩子生完了
we will get divorced.
咱俩就离了
I don't want to talk about divorce at all.
真的不能说离婚的事
I should sincerely apologize to you.
我跟你认真地道歉
I am sorry.
我错了
When I lose my temper,
我一发起脾气来
I often forget about your feelings
我就不顾你的感受
I took advantage of your kindness to me,
我仗着你对我好
yet I treated you badly.
我就欺负你
I really know I was wrong.
我 我真的知道错了
Could you please forgive me, Haowen?
你原谅我好不好 浩文
Haowen, Hao...
浩文 浩
Life is so short.
人生那么短
I want to live for myself.
我想为自己活着
I'll be free.
我就自由了
Please set me free.
你放我自由
I'm leaving.
我先走了
I want you to be around me.
我就愿意你围着我转
I want you to do it.
我就让你做
Let's set each other free, okay?
我们放过彼此 好不好
I just want to see you.
我就想看见你
I don't want you to let me go.
让你别放开我
Haowen!
浩文
Haowen, Haowen...
浩文 浩文
You don't need me anymore?
你不要我
and your children?
不要孩子了
No, dear.
不 老婆
I don't want this home.
这个家我不要
I'll leave it to you.
我都给你
I'm begging you.
我求求你了
Please give me another chance.
你再给我一次机会
I will listen to you.
我一定都听你的
I...
我
Haowen!
浩文
Where were you yesterday?
昨天你去哪儿了
Why didn't you answer my call?
我打电话你一直没接
I, I didn't.
我 我 没
You called me?
你给我打电话了
You still care about me.
你还是关心我的
Well, isn't it...
是不是
That...
那个
The thing in the safe is missing.
保险柜里的东西不见了
Did you take it?
是不是你拿的
I took it.
我拿走了
For the divorce.
要离婚了
I need to check the inventory of assets.
我清点一下家里的财产
Wait.
不是
OK.
那
Then I need to check the inventory too.
那我也要清点
So many years of marriage,
结婚这么多年
half of the family assets
家里的财产
belong to me, too.
也有我的一半
What belongs to you?
怎么就有你一半了
I've been working to support the family.
一直我在赚钱养家的
I've discussed it with the lawyer.
我跟律师都商量好了
The house, the car,
房子 车
and the family deposit is all yours.
家里的钱都是你的
Assets on the company's account is mine.
公司账上的都是我的
Why?
凭什么
We started the company together!
公司是咱俩一块儿开的
The name of the brand
品牌的名字
was named after me.
都是以我的名字命名的
That's last century's story.
那都猴年马月的事了
It's totally a new company today.
壳都换了好几波了
It has nothing to do with you at all.
跟你一点关系都没有
Jia Haowen.
贾浩文
I also hired a lawyer.
我也请了律师了
Don't think you can dump me casually.
你别想随随便便打发我
Fine.
行
Good, that's simple.
挺好的 事就简单了
I was afraid you didn't understand.
怕你不懂呢
Here is the divorce paper.
这是离婚协议书
If you agree with the terms I propose,
答应我的条件呢
we get divorced within a week.
一周之内离婚
If you don't,
如果你不答应
you will have nothing
除了公司的债务
except for the debt of the company.
你什么都没有
Asshole!
混蛋
Jia Haowen, you bastard.
贾浩文 你混蛋
Xin,
心心啊
how much you paid,
人付出多少
how much you will get.
才会得到多少
If you overdrew,
透支了
you will pay it back sooner or later.
早晚要还的
How to pay back?
怎么还
How will you pay back the years
我和孩子这么多年
me and your children staying with you?
你拿什么还
I will pay back what I owe you.
欠你的我一定会还
This is the emergency plan
这是我们内容部
drafted by our content department
根据现在的形势
according to the current situation.
做的应急方案
We'll immediately
我们马上
open a new account,
会开设新的账号
build a new backup platform.
打造新的备用平台
Then everyone,
那大家
do you have any comments?
还有其他意见吗
Big comment.
意见大了
Say it.
你说
In my opinion,
我说
the company account is monitored,
现在公司账号被监管
and the customers are withdrawing.
客户要撤
You only came up
你们就拿出
with this solution?
这么个方案来啊
What is this?
这什么玩意儿
Are you kidding me?
你们是在开玩笑吗
Kidding?
开玩笑
Is anyone in the content department
我们内容部的人
has time for kidding?
现在还有时间开玩笑
We need to implement rectification,
我们要落实整改
open a new account,
要开新账号
and build a new platform.
打造新平台
We have tried our best to retrieve.
我们真的在尽力挽回了
Ms. Huang,
黄副总啊
I think you can do nothing
我看您除了
except for pitching edge ball.
会打一点擦边球之外
Can't you do anything else?
是不是不会干别的了
Do you know how to make content?
你懂做内容吗
Do you know what kind of company
您了解我们新苗
Xinmiao is?
是一个什么样的公司吗
Mr. Zhou, Mr. Zhou.
周总 周总
If you really want to say something,
你要是真想说
say something constructive.
你就给点建设性的意见
Okay?
好吗
What's the use of personal attacks?
人身攻击有什么用啊
Personal attack?
人身攻击
I make personal attacks?
我人身攻击
Am I from the content department,
我是内容部的
or are you?
还是你是内容部的呀
Ms. Huang,
黄副总
who shall be responsible
公司造成
for the current situation
现在这样的局面
of the company today?
是谁的责任啊
Is it mine or yours?
是我的还是你的
A loss of tens of millions.
大几千万的损失
Will you or we pay for it?
你说是你赔还是我们赔
You examined the injury.
你验了伤
You still choose to sue Meng'an?
还要去告梦安啊
As a citizen,
作为公民
I have the right to hold her accountable.
我有追究她责任的权利
Then you make the company like this.
那你把公司搞成这样
Do I have the right
是不是我也有权利
to hold you accountable?
追究你的责任呢
Good.
好
We each bear our own responsibilities.
我们各负各的责任
Can you afford this responsibility?
这个责任你负得起吗
The company's account was banned.
公司被封号了
Investment has also been withdrawn.
投资也撤了
We lost tens of millions.
损失了几千万
Even if I
就算是我
don't hold you accountable.
不追究你的责任
Do you think the board
你以为董事会
will let you go?
能放得过你
Why don't you let Meng'an go.
这样吧 你放过梦安
And I will take care of it for you.
这件事情 我替你扛了
You still have to be working
你还要在这个行业里
in this industry for many years.
做下去
You don't need me to teach you, right?
怎么做不用我教你吧
Let's part on good terms.
好聚好散吧
Let Meng'an back and clean up the mess.
让梦安回来收拾烂摊子
I'm not going.
我可不去
What.
不是
Aren't you two friends?
你们俩关系不是好吗
Yes, we are friends.
关系好归关系好
But this shit?
这破事
It's not my business.
我不去
Wait, what's "this shit"?
不 这什么叫破事啊
Listen carefully,
我跟你说啊
you are from the HR Department.
你是人力资源部的
It's your business.
这事归你管
Oh, you're the boss.
那您还是老板呢
If you didn't indulge Huang Sisi,
你要不纵容黄思思
could Meng'an do this?
梦安能这样吗
Whom you offended yourself,
您自己得罪的人
go and bring her back yourself.
您自己去请
Don't, come on.
别别别
I'm begging you.
我求你们了
Don't treat me like that, okay?
别这么对待我 行不行
Look,
这样
you bring her back.
你负责把她请回来
I apologize to her.
我负责道歉
Is that okay?
你看行吗
Then show some sincerity.
那您拿出点诚意来
What sincerity?
我还怎么拿
Like this.
有
Hey, that's enough.
差不多得了啊
I'm your boss after all.
好歹我是你老板
Perfect.
好嘞
You rascals!
还反了你们了
Right.
对
Just throw these
就把这些
messy rubbish
乱七八糟的东西
all away.
都给我扔了
Throw as far as you can.
扔得越远越好
Anyone else can help?
还有人手吗
Come and help.
快过来帮忙
These, right, right.
这些 对对对
Throw them all out, all out.
都扔出去 扔出去
That,
那个
there are still some photos of Meng'an
梦安还有一些照片
in my office.
在我办公室
Go and get it later.
一会儿过去拿
OK.
好
Put them in order, to the original place.
摆整齐 恢复原样啊
You won.
你赢了
Not as happy as I thought.
也没想象中那么高兴
Now I know
我现在算是知道
what is the direct-line troops.
什么是嫡系部队了
You're pretty straightforward.
你还蛮直接的
That's who I am.
我这人就是这样
If I want something,
想要什么
I am always candid about it.
从来都是直接说直接做
Not like you,
不像你们
hypocritical.
虚伪
Do you know
知道
why you never became
为什么你一直没有成为
someone's direct-line buddy?
任何人的嫡系吗
Because you never
因为你没有
gave them reasons to trust you.
给他们信任的理由
I worked hard
我拼了命地工作
to achieve self-value.
努力实现自我价值
Am I wrong?
有错吗
You are not wrong.
没错
Then why you treated me like that?
那你们凭什么这么对我
How will Mr. Zhang
老张
deal with this matter?
要怎么处理这件事情啊
As long as I let you go,
只要我放过你
he will let me go.
他就放过我
You think it's unfair?
你觉得不公平
Of course.
当然
For the matter of my hitting you,
我打你这件事情呢
to the most,
最多就是接受
I will receive the punishment of Law of
《治安管理处罚法》的
Public Security Administration Punishment.
处罚
But for the damage you
但是你给公司
caused to the company,
造成的损失
the economic compensation to be paid,
带来的经济赔付
do you think
你觉得
they can be solved by
是《治安管理处罚法》
that Law?
能够解决的吗
So, who is Mr. Zhang
所以老张
protecting after all?
到底保下了谁啊
Honestly,
说实话啊
as far as this project is concerned,
就这个项目而言
if you operate it
以你的能力
with your normal capacity,
正常操作
you can do it really well.
都可以做得很好
But obviously you didn't.
但是很显然你没有
Because you wanted it so badly.
因为你心急
So, you chose the quick but dangerous path.
选择急功近利
But Huang Sisi,
但是黄思思
we should have a bottom line as a person.
我们做人要有底线
So does when we
做事
dealing with work.
更要
You may not know
你可能不知道
that I'm quite envious of you.
其实我挺羡慕你的
Young,
年轻
beautiful,
漂亮
competitive.
有能力
And hard working.
而且也敢拼
But whether it is
但是无论是你
the diligence
嘴巴里说的拼
or the excessive competition,
还是我们嘴巴里说的卷
it should be done properly.
都是要讲究方式方法的
This world
这个世界
has no shortcuts.
没有捷径
Because shortcut is biggest detour.
因为它是最大的弯路
Mr. Zhang, you're looking for me?
张总 你找我啊
What is it?
什么事
How's the cleaning up going
梦安的办公室
for the office of Meng'an?
收拾得怎么样了
Do you need my help?
要不要我帮忙
You? Then why we hire cleaners?
要您帮忙还要保洁干吗
You just deal with your own troubles.
您就收拾您的烂摊子吧
Is there anything else?
还有事吗
Meng'an, is she...
梦安那边 她 她
Just give her some time.
等等吧
As for the Valuation Adjustment Mechanism
蓝海最近的
financing scheme on Blue Ocean,
对赌融资方案
do you have any comments?
大家有什么建议
Since it's a VAM,
既然是对赌
it proves that Mr. Yu is
就足以证明于总对自己
very confident about himself.
是很有信心的
For us,
这对于我们来说嘛
it is also good news.
也是利好的
Xinmiao has been running poorly recently.
新苗公司最近经营不佳
It is rushing to get sold.
急着要卖掉
The price is also relatively reasonable.
价格也比较公道
Blue Ocean acquires Xinmiao.
蓝海吃下新苗
Then the local internet,
那么本地互联网
this piece of cake,
这块蛋糕
will belong to us.
就算是拉全了
It's like this.
是这样
Now,
现在
The world faced by Internet companies
互联网公司面对的环境
is that cruel.
就是这么残酷
Otherwise, the winner takes it all.
要不然就作为赢者通吃
Or you will die a beggar.
要不然就死无葬身之地
Wendy,
温蒂
What are your comments and suggestions?
你有什么意见和建议
I have nothing to suggest.
我没什么建议
Simply controlling the risk.
就是控制风险
The terms of the VAM proposed by Mr. Yu
于总都给了对赌的条件
show his sincerity.
我觉得他很有诚意了
Mr. Yu bears all the risks.
风险都于总自己担了
As the investor,
我们作为投资人
we are happy to see it.
当然很高兴
But Mr. Yu,
不过于总啊
please think clearly.
你可得想清楚了
It's not too late to regret.
现在后悔还来得及
Dear bosses,
各位大佬
you have trusted me so much,
已经这么相信我
and supported me so much.
这么支持我了
I will definitely do my best.
我一定全力以赴
Fine.
行
That's settled.
那就这么定了
Proceed with it.
往下推进
Hopefully we can soon
希望我们可以尽快
sign a tripartite agreement.
签订三方协议
Deal.
好
Ms Zhang,
张律师
did you see the pictures by paparazzi
我给你的狗仔拍的照片
that I gave to you?
你看了吗
I saw them.
看到了
I also looked into
我也调查了一下
the operation of Mr. Jia's
贾总公司近期的
company recently.
经营状况
Know myself and the enemy
知己知彼
is the way to defeat you.
才能够战胜你
This marriage defense.
这场婚姻保卫战
Your family's assets
你们家的财产
are basically accumulated after marriage.
基本上都是婚后累积的
As the law mandates,
法律规定
the family property after marriage
婚后的家庭财产
belongs to both spouses equally.
夫妻双方各占一半
But now we
但是我们现在
need to avoid that
要避免的就是
your husband
您的丈夫
hide your common property by
利用公司的股权
taking advantage of the company's
债权这种方式
equity and debt.
来藏匿你们的共同财产
I agree to divorce you.
我答应跟你离婚
Figured it out.
想通了
Let's meet
明天
tomorrow.
我们俩见一面吧
I'll decide the time and place.
时间地点我来定
I will say yes to anything
你只要来
as long as you show up.
我什么都答应你
OK. I can fulfill you.
好 成全你
Mr. Jia,
贾总
come in.
进来啊
Originally,
本来呢
I planned to visit Meng'an's home,
我是要去梦安家
and talked to her.
跟她谈的
But then I think
但我觉得
it is between the two of you.
这是你们两个人的事
So, it has to be solved in person.
还是得当面说
After all, it's been so many years.
毕竟这么多年了
There's nothing we can't speak about.
没什么不能说的
Apologize.
该道歉道歉
Make request.
该提要求提要求
As for who will get blackmailed at last,
至于谁能讹谁嘛
it's your show time.
各凭本事喽
I will avoid.
我回避了
Meng'an,
梦安哪
at work,
这工作上呢
we are a boss-employee relationship.
我们是上下级关系
But in life,
可是在生活里
you're my sister.
你就是我妹妹
Recently,
前一段时间呢
you have been reminding me.
你在不停地在提醒我
I know it in my heart that
哥心里都知道
the reminders were helpful.
提醒得都是对的
But I was
可是我当时
pushed too hard by them.
被他们逼得太紧了
So, I took a chance.
我就存了点侥幸心理
I thought I can rebound after this fight.
我想背水一战
Well,
就是
I didn't expect it would...
谁知道这
I was wrong, sister.
哥错了
How about this.
这样
I officially apologize to you.
哥正式给你道个歉
Mr. Zhang,
张总
no need for this between us.
咱俩就不用这样了吧
After all, I've been after you for years.
毕竟我跟着您这么多年
I still have loyalty to
对您和新苗
you and Xinmiao.
还都是有感情的
I,
我
let me put it this way.
这么说吧
You can have my words,
我还是那句话
that as long as I can work for one day,
但凡我还能上一天班
I will definitely do my best.
肯定会拼尽全力的
Well then,
那下面
content rectification will depend on you.
内容整改就交给你了
Whether the company can survive,
公司能不能存活
it's all up to you.
也都靠你了
To be honest
说实话
It's not that easy.
这个事也没那么容易的
But we need to act fast.
但是确实要抓紧
Because once it was banned too long,
因为封号时间一旦长了
it would be very difficult
再想启动
if we want to activate it again.
就太难了
Director Xu,
许总监啊
you are finally back!
可算回来了
I miss you so much.
我都想死你了
Why am I so unconvinced.
我怎么那么不相信呢
It's true.
是真的
When Ms. Huang was around,
那个姓黄的在的时候
I stood on your side faithfully.
我一直站在你这头的
She
那姓黄的
almost blew our
把咱们公司
company up.
弄得那是乌烟瘴气
A real mess!
乱七八糟啊
If we don't activate the account,
这要是再不开号
the company will be doomed.
我们公司可就垮了
Director Xu,
许总监 你是不知道
as soon as you left,
你这一走
the content department was in a mess!
这内容部都乱了套了
Our marketing department
我们市场部
was incriminated for that too.
都受到牵连啊
Tens of millions of compensations!
大几千万的赔款呀
Thank God you're back.
还好你回来了
Or those investors will
要不别人
sue me definitely.
就要跟我打官司了
Mr. Zhang,
张总
I said everything you wanted to say.
我把你想说的都说了
Don't bother to remind me that, get out.
用你说呀 你出去
Yeah. I get out. Out.
是 我出去 出去
It's nice to see you back, Director Xu.
回来就好 许总
Hurry up.
抓紧
Hurry up. Hurry up.
抓紧 抓紧
I will try my best.
我尽力
Why do you take me here?
你找我来这儿干什么
This warehouse
这个库房
is the starting point of our business.
是我们俩创业的起点
I've paid the rent for thirty years.
我交了三十年的租金
I thought you rent it to someone else.
我以为你租出去了呢
I won't get rich by that.
租也租不了几个钱
Keep it.
留着吧
As a memorial.
当个纪念
Fine.
行
Keep it if you like it.
你喜欢就留着
The lawyer is still waiting.
律师还等着呢
Hurry up and sign the agreement.
赶紧签协议去吧
Haowen,
浩文
do you remember this batch of goods?
你还记得这批货吗
The inventory of our online store.
开网店时候剩的
What?
怎么了
I still remember that
我还记得
the sales volume of the online shop
当年双十一的时候
was rocketing during the Double 11
我们家网店的
in those years.
销售情况很好
So, we took out all our savings
我们就把所有的积蓄
to make the patterns
都拿出来
of the clothes.
拿去打版
At that time, we thought
当时我们觉得
they would be a season hit,
一定能卖爆款
right?
对吧
But the sale volume was poor.
结果赔惨了
Traffic was diverted by the big brands.
流量都被大品牌吸走了
Tens of thousands of down jackets
一下子上万件羽绒服
were overstocked all at once.
全都砸在手里了
We owed a lot of money to
欠了原料商 代工厂
material suppliers and the factories.
一屁股的债
Do you remember?
你还记得呢
I still remember.
我还记得
To sell this batch of goods,
你为了销出去这批货
you traveled through the whole nation.
全国跑
From winter to summer.
从冬天一直跑到夏天
At last, you sold this batch of goods
才终于把这批货
a low price.
低价卖掉
And we recovered the loss a little.
总算挽回了一点损失
Then, we returned money to the suppliers
后来我们就原料厂
and contract factories.
代工厂
From one place to another.
一家一家地跑
To pay back money.
去还钱
Everyone thinks
所有人都觉得
that we can't pay this debt.
这笔账我们还不上了
But we did it anyway.
但我们还是做到了
Because of this credibility,
就是凭着这样的信誉
later they agreed
后来人家
to transact on credit.
才愿意给我们赊账
Later,
再后来
we found that copy patterns were not OK.
我们觉得打版不行了
We needed our own brand...
要做自己的品牌
Are you over?
说完了
Don't be sensational.
别煽情了啊
The lawyer is still waiting.
律师还等着呢
Sign the divorce papers quickly.
快签离婚协议吧
Jia Haowen,
贾浩文
when will you stop pretending?
你要装到什么时候
Pretending? What am I pretending?
我装什么了 我装
I give you one chance.
我就给你一次机会
Tell me the truth.
你给我说实话
The truth is,
实话就是
hurry up and sign the divorce papers.
赶紧签离婚协议吧
I received the notice from the bank
我收到银行通知了
You paid off the mortgage on the villa.
你把别墅的贷款还清了
Because I am the property owner.
因为房子是我的名字
You did this
这么做
simply to make sure
就是为了离婚之后
the villa could be mine completely
可以把房子
after the divorce, right?
分割给我 对吗
Yeah, I said that.
是啊 我说了
You will have the children and the house.
孩子 房子是你的
I will get the company.
公司是我的
That's what I said.
是我说的啊
What an actor.
演
Keep acting.
你再接着演
Where is the company?
公司都没有了
You don't have a company.
你有什么公司啊
I knew about the bankruptcy.
破产的事我知道了
And,
还有
you were beaten by the debt collectors.
你被人打的事
I also knew that.
我也知道了
You are such a slippery fellow.
你不讲究啊
You paid off the bank's mortgage,
有钱还银行的房贷
yet had no money to pay back our boss?
没钱还我们老板
Isn't it
是不是
something wrong with your character?
人品有问题
You need an education.
得教育
Carry on.
继续
The most valuable things in our house
家里所有值钱的东西
are all here.
都在这儿了
Plus this.
还有这个
Jia Haowen, listen to me carefully.
贾浩文 你给我听好了
I'm your wife.
我是你媳妇
I'm liable for your debts also.
所有的债我们一起扛
I won't let you face it alone.
我不会让你一个人扛的
Xin,
心
I don't want
我主要是不想
you and the kids get involved.
连累你跟孩子
What about you?
那你呢
Can you hide away forever?
你就一直东躲西藏的
Credibility is the most important.
做生意最重要的是信誉
Then you will
那你以后
never be an upright
也没有办法
man, and businessman
再堂堂正正地
once again.
做人 做生意了
I consulted with my lawyer.
我跟律师咨询过了
I have my way.
我有我的办法
You don't have to
这件事
worry about it.
你就不用管了
I also consulted my lawyer.
我也跟律师咨询过了
Instead of hiding away,
与其欠债东躲西藏的
why don't we pay back the debt,
不如把该还的都还了
and start over?
我们重新来过
How do we pay back so much money?
欠那么多钱怎么还啊
The lawyer analyzed the situation for me.
律师帮我分析了
I'll mortgage the villa
我把别墅
and the
还有你给我买的
small apartment
那套小公寓
you bought for me.
都拿去抵押了
The amount of the loans
拿来的钱
is almost enough to pay the debts.
差不多够你 还那些债
Darling,
老婆
I'm sorry.
对不起啊
When we got married, I swore
结婚的时候我发誓
to give you and the kids
要给你跟孩子
the best future.
最美好的未来
But I screwed it up.
但是让我给搞砸了
I'm really sorry.
真的对不起
When we got married,
那结婚的时候
we swore in front of the whole family,
我们还当着全家人的面
that
发誓呢
we will grow old together
说我们这辈子白头偕老
and never leave or give up on each other.
不离不弃的
We are far from it
这才哪儿到哪儿啊
You are already breaking your promise?
你就说话不算数了
Who do you think I am?
我是谁啊
I'm Xu Mengxin. I'm your wife.
我是许梦心 是你老婆
Can't let you say "divorce" and be done.
我能让你说离就离啊
If you dare to ask divorce again,
再敢跟我提离婚
believe it or not,
你信不信
I will marry someone else right away,
我带着两个孩子
with the two children.
转头就嫁人
You will never
让你这辈子
see Xiongxiong and Little Watermelon.
都看不到熊熊和小西瓜
I'm so sorry.
真对不起
I screwed it up.
就是我搞砸的
I'm sorry.
对不起啊
You fool.
傻子
Come over.
过来
Tell me about the nightclub?
夜总会是怎么回事啊
Oh, darling.
老婆
Mr. Jia,
贾总
come in.
进来啊
I knew you don't have the gut.
我就知道你没这个胆
Since when did you
你从什么时候
start to use two mobile phones?
开始有两个手机的
Mr. Jia,
贾总
come in.
进来啊
You don't need to go in.
你不用进去了
Didn't you say
你不是说
that you need pick up Meng'an later?
一会儿还要去接梦安吗
It's okay.
没事
Mr. Ma said that
这马院长吩咐了
we must take good care of you.
一定要把你照顾好
I am already well taken care of.
已经照顾得很好了
You picked me up at the airport.
亲自去机场接我
I'm very touched.
我很感动
Go back now.
快回去吧
In case your wife misunderstands it.
别让你们家领导误会
That's okay.
那行
Look,
这样
I'll pick you up tomorrow.
我明天来接你
And show you around our school.
去我们学校转悠一下
Take a look.
参观参观
OK.
好
But the thing I told you,
但是我跟你说的那件事
please think seriously about it.
你必须要认真考虑
Okay, sure.
好嘞 好嘞 好嘞
Okay, I'll see you tomorrow.
好 明天见啊
OK. OK.
好 好
Please take it for me.
帮我拿一下
Bye-bye.
拜拜 师哥
ID card.
身份证啊
Registered with the ID card.
身份证登记的
Just sign up.
报名就行了
Dear.
老婆
Here you come.
来啦
Why are you wearing slippers?
怎么穿 拖鞋
Are you OK?
怎么了
My feet are swollen.
脚肿了
Won't fit in leather shoes.
皮鞋穿不进去了
So, I bought a pair of slippers online.
外卖了双拖鞋
Do you need to go to the hospital?
要不要上医院看看
No need. It has swollen before.
不用 又不是没肿过
Exercise more.
多运动运动
Eat less salt.
少吃点盐 就行了
OK.
行
Sister is home.
姐在家
She cooked the anti-inflammatory soup.
还熬了排水的汤呢
Right.
对
Go home and have some soup.
回家喝汤
I'll drink some too.
我也喝点
You're swelling in feet as well?
你也肿了
A little.
我也有点肿
Share me some.
我蹭一点
What's in the back?
那后边放的什么呀
Mei Yiduo returned to China.
梅一朵回国了
The silk scarf for you.
给你带的丝巾
The chocolate for Yunjie.
给云阶带的巧克力
Your ex-girlfriend
你前女友
bought gifts for your wife and child.
给你老婆孩子买礼物
What's her intention?
她几个意思啊
And you picked her up?
你还替我们接了
What's your intention?
你是几个意思呀
Are you trying to be difficult now?
你这是打算作一会儿
Why can't I? Huh?
不行啊
Fine.
行
Then you tell me why she did all these.
那你说她几个意思
A man must be crystal clear about it
你说有女的
when there is a woman
喜欢你们男的
like him.
其实你们心里
It's obvious, isn't it?
都明明白白的 是吧
But I shouldn't take it.
但明白它不能接呀
Why?
怎么就不能接了呀
Inappropriate.
不合适嘛
Inappropriate for what?
哪不合适啊
It is inappropriate when I'm single.
这 单身的时候不合适
And it is even more inappropriate now.
那现在就更不合适了
Right?
对吧
Aren't you thinking about
那你现在就没想着
resuming the romance again?
再续前缘
What?
你是
Can you stop being so mean?
打算作到什么时候
Very soon.
快了
There's a red light ahead.
前方红灯了
This is an early warning.
这是预警了
Aren't you feeling so proud?
是不是心里头其实特美
What proud? No.
没有 美什么呀
Li Lin,
李临
does this silk scarf look good?
我这丝巾好看吗
You are not getting over with it, right?
这是没完了是吧
What's going on?
啥事啊
Very good!
好看
Very beautiful.
特别好看
It suits your skin well.
衬得你脸色特别好
Yes, mom. It is very beautiful.
是 妈 特别好看
Is the chocolate delicious?
巧克力好吃吗
Yummy.
好吃
Is there any more?
还有吗
The dad?
她爸
Sure.
有
She will have more.
必须有
Lin,
临临
I don't know
我怎么还不知道
you are such a good buyer!
你还这么会买东西啊
Sister.
姐
Yeah, he is good.
可会了
Eat your food.
吃饭